当应用启动时会默认执行MainActivity  在这个类的最下面
MainActivity is launched when you start the app. At the bottom of MainActivity,
有一个PlaceholderFragment  它是在我们创建项目的时候
we have PlaceholderFragment. PlaceholderFragment was generated by
生成的一个静态内部类
the template we used when creating our project.
fragment是Activity一个模块化的容器  在我们未来的课程中
A fragment is a modular container within your activity. In later lessons,
我们将会在一个Activity中使用多个fragment
we'll look at how to use multiple fragments in a single activity. And
我们也会再向大家详细解释  但是现在
we'll actually explain why, we're using them at all. But for now,
我们的Activity有一个fragment  这里这个PlaceholderFragment
our activity contains just this one fragment. So here in PlaceholderFragment,
是依据从布局资源文件里名为fragment_main的xml里生成的
is where we reference our UI layout resource, called fragment main.
这个XML文件项目文件在res目录下
This XML file lives in the Resource's RES directory of our Project Folder. You
你能看到各种各样的资源文件  除此之外你还能看到设计资源  比如
can see other kinds of resources here besides layouts, such as design assets or
drawables  strings  文件夹和文件  当我们的Activity执行时  它会根据
drawables, or strings. When our activity runs, it creates this placeholder
你的XML资源文件创建一个placeholderfragment布局  它会根据XML文件里
fragment which then inflates the XML layout resource, converting everything in
描述的对象视图等创建并放在内存里  点击ctrl键（Windows系统）
the XML file to a hierarchy of view objects in memory. By holding CTRL or
或者Mac系统下的Command键  然后点击fragment_main这个资源引用
CMD, depending on your operating system, and clicking on this reference to
Android Studio就会呈现一个图形化的编辑界面
fragment main. Android studio will drop us right into the visual layout editor.
如果是XML布局文件  我们就可以在下面切换到设计栏
Once we're inside a layout XML file, we can switch between the design tab,
我们可以通过拖拉控件的方式更直观的修改布局
where we can drag and drop new UI elements and modify the layout visually. And
在Text栏里  我们能阅读和修改布局中界面元素的原始XML代码
the Text tab, where we can see and edit the XML that defined the layout and
这里我们谈到的所有视图都是继承自基础视图类
UI elements. All of the views we'll talk about here ultimately extend the view
我们用的这个模板是一个RelativeLayout布局  都有
base class. The template we used gives us a relative layout, with some padding
边距等选项  我们稍后会再看一下这个布局的其他特点
around the edges. We'll get into layout features like padding and margins,
在这个RelativeLayout布局里面  是一个单独的TextView显示着 hello world
later. Inside our relative layout, is a single TextView that says, hello world.
EditText控件  就是一个可以输入文本的TextView
EditText, is a text entry field that is an editable version of text view.
他有很多选项  比如单行/多行显示
It has many options, such as whether it supports single or multi line.
EditText有多种预设的显示方式  在Text Field一栏里可以找到
There are several styled versions of editText, in the text field section of
比如姓名  电子邮件  手机号码  或者
android studio. Such as Name, E-mail, Phone, or
联系地址等  不同种类对应着不同的键盘输入模式
Postal Address. Each one sets the soft keyboard into an appropriate entry mode.
ImageView控件是根据他的source选项来显示图片的
ImageView displays the image defined in its source attribute.
它有很多种很方便的特点  比如根据你的设定
It has some really useful features. Like zooming and copying if the source file
自动伸缩适应
is to large or has a different aspect ratio than the image view itself.
ListView是一种特殊的视图  它的每一行都可以包含更多view
A list view is a special kind of view that contains one or
然后重复性的把视图和数据显示出来
more view that are replicated to display sets of data. In this
在我们这个课程里  TextView主要显示天气情况信息
case the single textView is used to display the weather information replicated
我们将会在之后的时间里详细介绍ListView
throughout the list. We'll get into much more detail about list view later on.